<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RIPx80</title>
    <link>https://meertec.de/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RIPx80</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Daniel Rittweiler</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 13:27:26 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://meertec.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Archlinux kernel configuration and compiling</title>
      <link>https://meertec.de/posts/arch-kernel-compiling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 13:27:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meertec.de/posts/arch-kernel-compiling/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is a short discurse about self kernel compilation on a arch system. Gentoo users are familiar with this kind of instructions or use the genkernel programm. You can find an article on https://wiki.archlinux.org/index.php/Kernels/Traditional_compilation
Install kernel sources and headers $ pacman -S base-devel # only gcc and make $ mkdir /usr/src/linux $ cd /usr/src/linux  download the newest kernel release, at this moment it is 4.13.0
$ wget https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Meertec</title>
      <link>https://meertec.de/posts/goodbye-meertec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 12:16:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meertec.de/posts/goodbye-meertec/</guid>
      <description>After a few years my website meertec.de which you can contact me for webdesign and other programming stuff goes offline.
Now my personal website ripx80 can find temp. on this domain. After registration you will be redirected to ripx80.info.
If you want some special or make me an offer, contact me about my e-mail address ripx80@protonmail.com
So goodbye meertec.de</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$ whoami Ripx80</title>
      <link>https://meertec.de/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 13:05:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meertec.de/about/</guid>
      <description>Introduction RIP is the Instruction Pointer of 64-Bit CPUs and he is interupting vector 0x80, on linux systems we use this for system_calls. The pseudo name was created when I read the Book &amp;ldquo;The Art of Exploitation&amp;rdquo; since few years and handle with the EIP on 64-Bit systems :-).
I love the linux system and uses Gentoo if I have a lot of time and for security proposes. But when I have some trouble in the year I switch to Arch Linux&amp;hellip; because I have not 45min to compile the newest firefox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://meertec.de/legal_disclosure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 14:00:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meertec.de/legal_disclosure/</guid>
      <description>Information in accordance with section 5 TMGRittweiler, DanielRoonstra&amp;szlig;e 1265195 WiesbadenContactTelephone: 105405050E-Mail: ripx80@protonmail.comWebsite: https://ripx80.ioPerson responsible for content in accordance with 55 Abs. 2 RStVDaniel Rittweiler
Roonstra&amp;szlig;e 12
65195 WiesbadenDisclaimerAccountability for contentThe contents of our pages have been created with the utmost care. However, we cannot guarantee the contents&amp;rsquo; accuracy, completeness or topicality. According to statutory provisions, we are furthermore responsible for our own content on these web pages. In this context, please note that we are accordingly not obliged to monitor merely the transmitted or saved information of third parties, or investigate circumstances pointing to illegal activity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>